A Guide to the Pete Calos Photograph Collection, 1977-2005
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Virginia Diners., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  - L & S Diner - Liberty Street, Harrisonburg - interior with patrons - (Othertype 1:480)
  - Court Square - Harrisonburg - exterior - (Othertype 1:481)
  - Jess' Quick Lunch - Harrisonburg - exterior - (Othertype 1:482)
  - Jess' Quick Lunch - Harrisonburg - showing pot on stove - (Othertype 1:483)
  - Jess' Quick Lunch - Harrisonburg - interior counter - (Othertype 1:484)
  - Elkton - street by railroad - (Othertype 1:485)
  - Ray's Diner - Elkton - exterior - (Othertype 1:486)
  - Ray's Diner - Elkton - grilled cheese, burgers on grill - (Othertype 1:487)
  - Ray's Diner - Elkton - interior counter - (Othertype 1:488)
  - Ray's Diner - Elkton - interior with patrons - (Othertype 1:489)
  - Pink Cadillac Diner - Greenville - sign - (Othertype 1:490)
  - Pink Cadillac Diner - Greenville - Pink Cadillac car outside - (Othertype 1:491)
  - Pink Cadillac Diner - Greenville - interior - (Othertype 1:492)
  - Pink Cadillac Diner - Greenville - Elvis lamp - (Othertype 1:493)
  - Texas Inn - Lynchburg - exterior - (Othertype 1:494)
  - Texas Inn - Lynchburg - interior - (Othertype 1:495)
  - Texas Inn - Lynchburg - wall menus - (Othertype 1:498)
  - Walker's Diner - N. Main Street, Farmville - exterior - (Othertype 1:496)
  - Walker's Diner - N. Main Street, Farmville - street view - (Othertype 1:497)
  - Walker's Diner - N. Main Street, Farmville - exterior - (Othertype 1:498)
  - Horse-shoe Restaurant - Danville - interior - (Othertype 1:499)
  - Horse-shoe Restaurant - Danville - exterior - (Othertype 1:500)
  - Horse-shoe Restaurant - Danville - sign - (Othertype 1:501)
  - Horse-shoe Restaurant - Danville - horse shoe counter - (Othertype 1:502)
  - Horse-shoe Restaurant - Danville - interior tables - (Othertype 1:503)
  - Horse-shoe Restaurant - Danville - Annie Skipwith, cook - (Othertype 1:504)
  - Chatham - showing Rt. 57 into Main Street - (Othertype 1:505)
  - Bill's Diner - Chatham - exterior with sign; Street Car Named Desire - (Othertype 1:506)
  - Burnett's Diner - S. Main Street, Chatham - street view - (Othertype 1:507)
  - Burnett's Diner - S. Main Street, Chatham - railroad car diner exterior - (Othertype 1:508)
  - Burnett's Diner - S. Main Street, Chatham - detail of entrance - (Othertype 1:509)
  - Burnett's Diner - S. Main Street, Chatham - interior - (Othertype 1:510)
  - Burnett's Diner - S. Main Street, Chatham - interior counter - (Othertype 1:511)
  - View of W.D. Rowe Monuments and Little Chef Diner - Danville - (Othertype 1:512)
  - Little Chef Diner - Danville - exterior - (Othertype 1:513)
  - Little Chef Diner - Danville - makers plate; Valentine Manufacturing Company - (Othertype 1:514)
  - Little Chef Diner - Danville - interior - (Othertype 1:515)
  - Heart Line Restaurant - Danville - exterior - (Othertype 1:516)
  - Heart Line Restaurant - Danville - interior - (Othertype 1:517)
  - Heart Line Restaurant - Danville - interior - (Othertype 1:518)
  - Roanoke Wiener Stand - interior counter with patron - (Othertype 1:519)
  - Roanoke Wiener Stand - downtown exterior - (Othertype 1:520)
  - Roanoke Wiener Stand - front exterior - (Othertype 1:521)
  - Roanoke Wiener Stand - chart illustrating the rising cost of hot dog - (Othertype 1:522)
  - Roanoke Wiener Stand - Charlie Thomas, cook - (Othertype 1:523)
  - Roanoke Wiener Stand - hot dogs, chili, coke - (Othertype 1:524)
  - Roanoke Wiener Stand - counter and patrons - (Othertype 1:525)
  - Roanoke Wiener Stand - counter and patrons - (Othertype 1:526)
  - Roanoke Wiener Stand - WWII Poster; Some birds talk too much - (Othertype 1:527)
  - Hillsville Diner - street view - (Othertype 1:528)
  - Hillsville Diner,(moved from Mt. Airy in 1946) - exterior - (Othertype 1:529)
  - Hillsville Diner - Mac McPeak, owner - (Othertype 1:530)
  - Hillsville Diner - interior - (Othertype 1:531)
  - Hillsville Diner - interior counter with patrons - (Othertype 1:532)
  - Hillsville Diner - wood paneled booth - (Othertype 1:533)
  - Hillsville Diner - kitchen - (Othertype 1:534)
  - Hillsville Diner - exterior - (Othertype 1:535)
  - Mackie's - Martinsville - exterior - (Othertype 1:536)
  - Thomas House Restaurant - Dayton - counter - (Othertype 1:537)
  - Thomas House Restaurant - Dayton - sign - (Othertype 1:538)
  - Thomas House Restaurant - Dayton - front exterior - (Othertype 1:539)
- Series VI: Virginia Lighthouses., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  Virginia Lighthouses document active and historically significant Virginia Lighthouses during the period of 1995 through 2003.
  Arrangement: Maintained in original order.
  L
  IGHTHOUSES REPRESENTED IN THIS COLLECTION:
  Name - Location- Date of First Light
  Assateague Light - Accomack County - (1867)
  Cape Henry Light - Virginia Beach - (1792 AND 1881)
  Chesapeake Light - East Northeast of Cape Henry - (1965)
  Jones Point Light - Alexandria - (1856)
  Jordan Point Light - South approach of Benjamin Harrison Bridge, East of Hopewell - (1895)
  New Point Comfort Light - Mathews County - (1806)
  Newport News Middle Ground (Shoal) Light - Newport News - (1891)
  Old Point Comfort Light - Hampton - (1802)
  Rappahanock Shoal Channel, S. Range Rear - Cheasapeake Bay off Silver Beach, S.W. of Jamesville - (1991)
  Smith Point Light - Northumberland County, Entrance to Potomac River - (1897)
  Thimble Shoal Light - Hampton Roads - (1914)
  Wolf Trap Light - A shoal in the Chesapeake Bay S. of the mouth of the Rappahannock -(1894)
  - Assateague Lighthouse - Accomack County - tower- (Othertype 1:540)
  - Assateague Lighthouse - Accomack County - tower and keeper house- (Othertype 1:541)
  - Jones Point Lighthouse - Alexandria, on Potomac River - keeper house - (Othertype 1:542)
  - New Point Comfort Lighthouse - Mathews County - tower - (Othertype 1:543)
  - Jordan Point Lighthouse - Hopewell, on James River beside Benjamin Harrison Bridge - (Othertype 1:544)
  - Jordan Point Lighthouse - Hopewell - house - (Othertype 1:545)
  - Jordan Point Lighthouse - Hopewell - showing light scafolding - (Othertype 1:546)
  - Old Point Comfort Lighthouse - Fort Monroe, Hampton - (Othertype 1:547)
  - Old Point Comfort Lighthouse - Fort Monroe, Hampton - house and light tower (Othertype 1:548)
  - Old Point Comfort Lighthouse - Fort Monroe, Hampton - detail top of tower - (Othertype 1:549)
  - Old Point Comfort Lighthouse - Fort Monroe, Hampton - cat grave - (Othertype 1:550)
  - Portsmouth Lightship - Portsmouth - (Othertype 1:551)
  - Old & New Cape Henry Lighthouse - Virginia Beach at the point - (Othertype 1:552)
  - Old & New Cape Henry Lighthouse - Virginia Beach - step entrance of Old with New - (Othertype 1:553)
  - Old Cape Henry Lighthouse - Virginia Beach - interior winding steps - (Othertype 1:554)
  - New Cape Henry Lighthouse - Virginia Beach - through top panes of Old Lighthouse - (Othertype 1:555)
  - New Cape Henry Lighthouse - Virginia Beach - sunshine view - (Othertype 1:556)
  - New Cape Henry Lighthouse - Virginia Beach - rain view - (Othertype 1:557)
  - New Cape Henry Lighthouse - Virginia Beach - detail of top - (Othertype 1:558)
  - Smith Point Lighthouse - Northumberland County - where Potomac enters Cheasapeake Bay - (Othertype 1:559)
  - Rappahannock Shoal Channel South Range Light Station - (Othertype 1:560)
  - Thimble Shoal Light - Hampton Roads - entrance to Hampton Roads - (Othertype 1:561)
  - Old Point Comfort from water - Fort Monroe, Hampton - (Othertype 1:562)
  - Old Point Comfort from water - Fort Monroe, Hampton - (Othertype 1:563)
  - Middle Ground Lighthouse with boat - Newport News - (Othertype 1:564)
  - Middle Ground Lighthouse - Newport News - (Othertype 1:565)
  - Wolf Trap Light - Mathews County - (Othertype 1:566)
  - Wolf Trap Light - Mathews County - (Othertype 1:567)
- Series VII: Route One., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  The Route One series records hotels, businesses, homes, and attractions along the Virginia section of this eastern seaboard roadway. Also known as U.S. Rt. 1 or Jefferson Davis Highway, the roadway opened in 1926. From 1997 to 2001 Calos recorded select locations of the Virginia portion, from Arlington in the North to Woodbridge in the South.
  - View of Washington, D.C. - at 14th Street Bridge - (Othertype 1:568)
  - Historic sign for Route One - Fairfax County - (Othertype 1:569)
  - Masonic Temple - Alexandria - (Othertype 1:570)
  - Unnamed Motel - South Fairfax County - (Othertype 1:571)
  - Woodlawn Plantation - Fairfax County - (Othertype 1:572)
  - David Norman's Shell Station - Fredericksburg - (Othertype 1:573)
  - Old Pump, Shell Station - Fredericksburg (Othertype 1:574)
  - David Norman in Garden - behind Shell Station - (Othertype 1:575)
  - Abandoned Motel - (Othertype 1:576)
  - Falmouth Church - (Othertype 1:577)
  - Rappahannock River Bridge - (Othertype 1:578)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars sign - (Othertype 1:579)
  - Ni River - Massaponax, Spotsylvania County - (Othertype 1:580)
  - Arcadia Store - Built 1925 - (Othertype 1:581)
  - Arcadia Store - (Othertype 1:582)
  - Building - Thornburg - (Othertype 1:583)
  - Glass House Restaurant - (Othertype 1:584)
  - Closed building - (Othertype 1:585)
  - Hilltop Motel - (Othertype 1:586)
  - CCC Road - Route 1 and Route 606 - (Othertype 1:587)
  - Log Cabin Motel - (Othertype 1:588)
  - Carmel Church - (Othertype 1:589)
  - Brick Building - Carmel Church - (Othertype 1:590)
  - Collapsed building - (Othertype 1:591)
  - Rain-bow Lite Restaurant - (Othertype 1:592)
  - Beverly's Grill - (Othertype 1:593)
  - Ellington - (Othertype 1:594)
  - WWII Quonset Huts - (Othertype 1:595)
  - House in disrepair - (Othertype 1:596)
  - Long Creek - (Othertype 1:597)
  - Hanover tomato stand - (Othertype 1:598)
  - Riverview Garage - Hanover County - (Othertype 1:599)
  - Bridge and Grain silos - South Anna River - (Othertype 1:600)
  - Mill - South Anna River - (Othertype 1:601)
  - Best Products Warehouse - (Othertype 1:602)
  - Entering the town of Ashland - (Othertype 1:603)
  - Smokey Pig Restaurant - Ashland - (Othertype 1:604)
  - Wigwam - (Othertype 1:605)
  - Rosebowl Drive in Movie Theater - (Othertype 1:606)
  - Snow White Inn - (Othertype 1:607)
  - St. Joseph's Villa - (Othertype 1:608)
  - Richmond City Limits - (Othertype 1:609)
  - Haynes Jeep - Used Cars - (Othertype 1:610)
  - Haynes Jeep - Used Cars - side and tiled roof - (Othertype 1:611)
  - Ginter Park School - (Othertype 1:612)
  - Belvidere & Broad - (Othertype 1:613)
  - Richmond Tobacco Company building - (Othertype 1:614)
  - Milestone 3 - Marker at Tobacco Company building - (Othertype 1:615)
  - Kelly's hamburgers - (Othertype 1:616)
  - Filippo's Ford sign - (Othertype 1:617)
  - Filippo's Dancing - (Othertype 1:618)
  - Psychic Reader House - (Othertype 1:619)
  - Palm Reader Building - (Othertype 1:620)
  - Fort Darling Motel - (Othertype 1:621)
  - Farm House Restaurant - (Othertype 1:622)
  - Chimney Corner Motel - (Othertype 1:623)
  - Pandy's Peanuts - abandoned drive-in - (Othertype 1:624)
  - Subway - (Othertype 1:625)
  - Bellwood Manor - (Othertype 1:626)
  - Sign for Highway Route One - South - (Othertype 1:627)
  - Colony Inn - (Othertype 1:628)
  - Halfway House Restaurant - (Othertype 1:629)
  - Dutch Gap Cabin - (Othertype 1:630)
  - Moore's Cabin - (Othertype 1:631)
  - Moore's Cabin Restaurant - (Othertype 1:632)
  - Moore's Cabin Restaurant - (Othertype 1:633)
  - Skye's Antiques - (Othertype 1:634)
  - Sign for Coldbrook Motel - (Othertype 1:635)
  - Coldbrook Motel - (Othertype 1:636)
  - TS's Motel - (Othertype 1:637)
  - Swift Creek Mill - (Othertype 1:638)
  - Appomattox River - Petersburg - (Othertype 1:639)
  - St. Andrew's Catholic Church - Petersburg - (Othertype 1:640)
  - First Baptist Church - (Othertype 1:641)
  - Folly Castle - (Othertype 1:642)
  - Old Petersburg High School - (Othertype 1:643)
  - Kings Barbeque - (Othertype 1:644)
  - Kitchen's Cabins - (Othertype 1:645)
  - Tartane's Cottages - (Othertype 1:646)
  - Blue Tartane - cottage - (Othertype 1:647)
  - Georgian Motel - (Othertype 1:648)
  - Stuckey's - (Othertype 1:649)
  - Bridge on Stony Creek - (Othertype 1:650)
  - Bridge on Stony Creek - (Othertype 1:651)
  - Fire Tower and sign - (Othertype 1:652)
  - Fire Tower - (Othertype 1:653)
  - W. Boisseau's Store - (Othertype 1:654)
  - W. Boisseau's Store - watermelon stand - (Othertype 1:655)
  - McKenney- Tin Man - (Othertype 1:656)
  - Wilmurt's Motel - now Scottish Inn - (Othertype 1:657)
  - Jefferson Davis Highway dedication marker - United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1931 - (Othertype 1:658)
  - Nottoway Restaurant - (Othertype 1:659)
  - Meredithville Post Office - (Othertype 1:660)
  - Funeral Home - (Othertype 1:661)
  - Horse-shoe Restaurant - South Hill - (Othertype 1:662)
  - Motel Restaurant - abandoned - (Othertype 1:663)
  - Steel Bridge Mini-Mart building - (Othertype 1:664)
  - Building with "Virginia" sign marking State line - (Othertype 1:665)
  - Pete Calos with vintage Mercedes - (Othertype 1:666)
- Series VIII: Small Town, U.S.A., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  Small Town, U.S.A. records the characteristic appearance that many small towns in the South share. Calos documents stores, businesses, restaurants, and roadsides along the outskirts of town to the quaint Main Streets downtown. The "vintage" look to these images was due to an processing error in the color film. The resulting change from color to tinted black and white was accidental, but it appealed to Calos' and he accepted the gaffe as art by accident, due to the vintage quality it bestows on the subjects.
  - Bank of Carson, Carson - (Othertype 1:667)
  - Mansion in Carson, Carson - (Othertype 1:668)
  - Railroad Station, Carson - (Othertype 1:669)
  - Bar-B-Q, Stoney Creek - (Othertype 1:670)
  - A & B Market, Jarratt - (Othertype 1:671)
  - Old Store, Dinwiddie Court House - (Othertype 1:672)
  - Molone's Place, Richmond - (Othertype 1:673)
  - Stucco building, Mckenney - (Othertype 1:674)
  - Baxter's Pharmacy, Mckenney - (Othertype 1:675)
  - Clock, Dinwiddie - (Othertype 1:676)
  - Building, Alberta - (Othertype 1:677)
  - Boydton Town Office, Boydton - (Othertype 1:678)
  - Mechlenburg County Court House - (Othertype 1:679)
  - Boyd's Tavern - (Othertype 1:680)
  - Virgilina Town Hall - (Othertype 1:681)
  - Virgilina Town Hall (color) - (Othertype 1:682)
  - Virgilina Railroad Station - (Othertype 1:683)
  - Halifax Damask Mill tower, South Boston - (Othertype 1:684)
  - Callie Army Surplus, South Boston - (Othertype 1:685)
  - Barber Shop, Blackstone - (Othertype 1:686)
  - Post Office, Nottoway - (Othertype 1:687)
  - Hotel, Crewe - (Othertype 1:688)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars Tank, Crewe - (Othertype 1:689)
  - Burke Lodge, AF & AM, Burkeville - (Othertype 1:690)
  - Burkeville Funeral home, Insurance building - (Othertype 1:691)
  - Main Street, Burkeville - (Othertype 1:692)
  - Post Office, Burkeville - (Othertype 1:693)
  - Cement Plant, Drakes Branch - (Othertype 1:694)
  - Victorian Home, Drakes Branch - (Othertype 1:695)
  - Tommy's Auto, Drakes Branch - (Othertype 1:696)
  - Main Street Drakes Branch - (Othertype 1:697)
  - Municipal Bank, Drakes Branch - (Othertype 1:698)
  - Fire Department, Drakes Branch - (Othertype 1:699)
  - Va. Southern Railroad, Keysville - (Othertype 1:700)
  - Va. Southern Railroad, Keysville - (Othertype 1:701)
  - Va. Southern Railroad, Keysville - (Othertype 1:702)
  - Va. Southern Railroad, Keysville - (Othertype 1:703)
  - Va. Southern Railroad, Keysville - (Othertype 1:704)
  - Va. Southern Railroad, Keysville - (Othertype 1:705)
  - Va. Southern Railroad, Keysville - (Othertype 1:706)
  - Dixie Lee Warehouse, Kenbridge - (Othertype 1:707)
  - Bar-B-Q Kenbridge - (Othertype 1:708)
  - Mable's Hair Place, Waverly - (Othertype 1:709)
  - Store front, Claremont - (Othertype 1:710)
  - Victorian house, Claremont - (Othertype 1:711)
  - House, Claremont - (Othertype 1:712)
  - Mason-Dixon Line Gas station - (Othertype 1:713)
- Series IX: Works Progress Administration Post Office Murals., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  The W. P.A. Mural series documents original art work commissioned by the Works Progress Administration's, Section of Fine Arts for public buildings during 1934-1943. Popularly called The Section, the operation was headed by Edward Bruce, and administered by the Procurement Division of the Treasury Department. The program operated as incentive to put artisans to work during the Depression years by awarding commissions for installation of murals in public buildings. Calos concentrated on recording murals still accessible in Post Offices throughout Virginia from 1997 to 2001. It should be noted that several have been removed to new locations since the time of photography.
  W
  .P.A. MURAL ARTISTS REPRESENTED IN THIS COLLECTION:
  Artist - Life Dates - Location of Mural
  Edmund Archer (1904-1986) - Hopewell
  Auriel Bessemer (1909-1986) - Arlington
  Sarah Blakeslee - Strasburg
  Florence Bessom (b.1905) - Staunton
  Paul Cadmus (1994-1999) - Richmond Parcel Post Building
  William H. Calfee (1909-1955) - Harrisonburg, Petersburg, Phoebus, and Tazewell
  Walter Carnelli (1905-1959) - Bassett
  William Abbott Cheever - Smithfield
  Alexander B. Clayton (b.1906) - Radford (mural covered)
  John E. Costigan (1888-1972) - Stuart
  Carson Davenport (1908-1972) - Chatham
  John W. de Groot - christiansburg
  Mary B. Fowler - Newport News, Virginia Beach Customs House
  Jared French (1905-1987) - Richmond Parcel Post Building
  Arnold Friedman (1874-1946) - Orange County
  Roy Hilton (1891-1963) - Rockymount
  Sheffield Kagy (1907-1989) - Luray
  Richard Kenah (1907-1982) - Bluefield
  Edwin S. Lewis - Berryville and Petersburg
  Herman Maril (1908-1986) - Alta Vista
  Daniel Olney (b. 1909) - Marion
  John H.R. Pickett - Virginia Beach
  Andree Ruellan (b.1905) - Emporia
  Lenore Thomas (1909-1988) - Covington
  - VA Beach Coast Guard Station - (Othertype 1:714)
  - VA Beach Post Office - (Othertype 1:715)
  - VA Beach Post Office: Arrival of Whites in Jamestown - oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:716)
  - VA Beach Post Office: Arrival of Whites in Jamestown - Indians - oil on canvas detail - (Othertype 1:717)
  - VA Beach Post Office: Arrival of Whites in Jamestown - Slaves - oil on canvas detail - (Othertype 1:718)
  - VA Beach Post Office: Arrival of Whites in Jamestown - Women - oil on canvas detail - (Othertype 1:719)
  - VA Beach Post Office: Arrival of Whites in Jamestown, Women - oil on canvas detail - (Othertype 1:720)
  - VA Beach Post Office: Arrival of Whites in Jamestown, Women - oil on canvas detail - (Othertype 1:721)
  - Downtown Phoebus: View from across the Post Office - (Othertype 1:722)
  - Phoebus Post Office - (Othertype 1:723)
  - Phoebus Post Office: Under construction, circa 1938 - (Othertype 1:724)
  - Phoebus Post Office: Brass Mail Box - detail - (Othertype 1:725)
  - Phoebus Post Office: Cheasapeake Fisherman - fresco - (Othertype 1:726)
  - Phoebus Post Office: Cheasapeake Fisherman - fresco, detail - (Othertype 1:727)
  - Phoebus Post Office: Cheasapeake Fisherman - fresco, detail - (Othertype 1:728)
  - Phoebus Post Office: Artist, William Calfee's signature on boat bow - fresco - (Othertype 1:729)
  - Virginia Beach: Victory Arch- built 1918 - (Othertype 1:730)
  - Newport News: Virginia Beach Customs House, built 1904 - (Othertype 1:731)
  - VA Beach Customs House: Christopher Newport Bringing News and Aid to the Starving Indians - unglazed terra-cotta - (Othertype 1:732)
  - VA Beach Custom House: Sitting Indian - unglazed terra-cotta freeze - (Othertype 1:733)
  - Smithfield Station - (Othertype 1:734)
  - Smithfield Post Office - exterior - (Othertype 1:735)
  - Smithfield Post Office: Captain John Smith Trading with the Indians - oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:736)
  - Smithfield Post Office: Captain John Smith Trading with the Indians - oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:737)
  - Smithfield Post Office: Captain John Smith Trading with the Indians - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:738)
  - Smithfield Post Office: Captain John Smith Trading with the Indians - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:739)
  - Emporia: Klugel Iron Works - (Othertype 1:740)
  - Emporia: Klugel Iron Works - Hotel Virginia sign - (Othertype 1:741)
  - Emporia Post Office - exterior - (Othertype 1:742)
  - Emporia Post Office: Country Saw Mill - oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:743)
  - Emporia Post Office: Country Saw Mill, Horse wagon - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:744)
  - Emporia Post Office: Country Saw Mill, Logging - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:745)
  - Petersburg Court House - (Othertype 1:746)
  - Petersburg Post Office: Harvesting Tobacco - oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:747)
  - Petersburg Post Office: Harvesting Tobacco - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:748)
  - Petersburg Post Office: Harvesting Tobacco - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:749)
  - Petersburg Post Office: Harvesting Tobacco - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:750)
  - Petersburg Post Office: Riding to Hounds - oil on canvas- (Othertype 1:751)
  - Petersburg Post Office: Riding to Hounds - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:752)
  - Hopewell Post Office - exterior - (Othertype 1:753)
  - Hopewell Post Office: Captain Francis Eppes making Friends with the Appomatox Indians - oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:754)
  - Hopewell Post Office: Captain Francis Eppes - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:755)
  - Hopewell Post Office: Captain Francis Eppes - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:756)
  - Hopewell Post Office: Appomattox Indian - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:757)
  - Hopewell Post Office: Appomattox Indian - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:758)
  - Hopewell Post Office: Artist, Edmund Archer's signature on foot - detail, oil on canvas - (Othertype 1:759)
  - Hopewell Post Office: Origin of Hopewell print - print framed - (Othertype 1:760)
  - Richmond: City Limits marker - (Othertype 1:761)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building - (Othertype 1:762)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building - corner stone - (Othertype 1:763)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building - (Othertype 1:764)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Pocahontas Saving John Smith - mural - (Othertype 1:765)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Sir Walter Raleigh - mural panel - (Othertype 1:766)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: William Byrd - mural panel - (Othertype 1:767)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Pocahontas Saving John Smith - mural - (Othertype 1:768)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Pocahontas Saving John Smith - mural detail - (Othertype 1:769)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Pocahontas Saving John Smith - detail with flash - (Othertype 1:770)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Pocahontas - detail with flash - (Othertype 1:771)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Pocahontas - mural detail of Indians- (Othertype 1:772)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Pocahontas - detail Indian with mask - (Othertype 1:773)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Stuart's Raiders at the Swollen Fords - mural detail - (Othertype 1:774)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Jeb Stuart - mural side panel - (Othertype 1:775)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: John Pelham - mural side panel - (Othertype 1:776)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Stuart's Raiders - mural detail - (Othertype 1:777)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Stuart's Raiders - mural detail - (Othertype 1:778)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Stuart's Raiders - mural detail - (Othertype 1:779)
  - Richmond: Parcel Post Building: Stuart's Raiders - mural detail - (Othertype 1:780)
  - Ashland Post Office- built 1940 - (Othertype 1:781)
  - Orange County Court House - (Othertype 1:782)
  - Orange County Post Office - (Othertype 1:783)